Franz Boas Papers 1862-1942 Mss.B.B61.eleven Mss.B.B61.inventory11
American Philosophical Society
Franz Boas Papers: Inventory (R)
1862-1942
Mss.B.B61.inventory11
American Philosophical Society
1.0 section
This is part of the large inventory for the Franz Boas Papers (Mss B B61). For complete information concerning this collection, please view the Collection Description.
Boas, Franz, 1858-1942
Scope and Contents note
Due to the size of the collection, the content for Series I has been divided into multiple inventories. Please follow the links below to browse the inventories.
Inventories
Correspondents A
Correspondents B
Correspondents C
Correspondents D
Correspondents E-G
Correspondents H
Correspondents I-K
Correspondents L
Correspondents M
Correspondents N-Q
Correspondents R
Correspondents S
Correspondents T-V
Correspondents W-Z
- Franz Boas Papers - Correspondents R
  - R_____, G.P. (Box 73)
    - RE: Rev. Francis (Franz) Gross, 1933 Sep. 20; 3p
  - Rabi, Mrs. (Box 73)
    - From Meehan, Marjorie C., 1938 Oct. 26
  - Rabinowitz, M.A. (Box 73)
    - From Boas, 1933 Nov. 24; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 Nov. 11; 1p
  - Racca, V. (Box 73)
    - From Boas, 1936 July 1
    - From Boas, 1936 June 19
    - To Boas, 1936 June 22
    - To Boas, 1936 June 29
      - re: Italians of N. Haven, 1936 June 30; 11p
      - re: Italians of N. Haven, 1936 June 30; 4p
    - To Boas, 1936 July 3
  - "Race" (Box 73)
    Scope and Contents note
    See Johnson, Alvin
  - Racial Education in the Schools (Box 73)
    - From Hitler Jugend, Munich, 1935 Nov. 23; 3p
      - enc. with Wallach, S., 1936 Feb. 14
  - Radcliffe-Brown, A.R. (Box 73)
    - To Boas, 1931 Dec. 17
  - Rader, Melvin (Box 73)
    - To Boas, 1939 May 1
  - Radermacher (Box 73)
    - To Boas, 1928 Apr. 26
  - Radin, Paul (Box 73)
    - From Boas, 1908 June 1
    - From Boas, 1909 Apr. 2
    - From Boas, 1909 Apr. 6
    - From Boas, 1911 Nov. 8
    - From Boas, 1912 Sep. 12
    - From Boas, 1912 Oct. 26; 3p
    - From Boas, 1912 Nov. 19; 2p
    - From Boas, 1912 Nov. 25; 2p
    - From Boas, 1912 Nov. 27
    - From Boas, 1912 Dec. 3
    - From Boas, 1912 Dec. 16
    - From Boas, 1913 Jan. 3
    - From Boas, 1913 Jan. 14
    - From Boas, 1913 Jan. 27
    - From Boas, 1913 Feb. 4; 2p
    - From Boas, 1913 July 23; 2p
    - From Boas, 1913 Nov. 5
    - From Boas, 1913 Nov. 17
    - From Boas, 1913 Dec. 1
    - From Boas, 1913 Dec. 17
    - From Boas, 1914 Feb. 7
    - From Boas, 1914 Mar. 16; 2p
    - From Boas, 1914 Mar. 25; 2p
    - From Boas, 1914 Apr. 4
    - From Boas, 1914 Dec. 21; 2p
    - From Boas, 1915 Jan. 2
    - From Boas, 1916 Jan. 17
    - From Boas, 1916 Jan. 18
    - From Boas, 1916 Feb. 16
    - From Boas, 1916 Feb. 23; 2p
    - From Boas, 1916 Apr. 6; 2p
    - From Boas, 1916 Apr. 24; 2p
    - From Boas, 1916 Oct. 17
    - From Boas, 1917 Jan. 10
    - From Boas, 1917 Jan. 19
    - From Boas, 1917 Feb. 27
    - From Boas, 1918 Feb. 4
    - From Boas, 1920 May 6
    - From Boas, 1920 Oct. 25
    - From Boas, 1921 Feb. 4
    - From Boas, 1924 Nov. 12
    - From Boas, 1924 Dec. 29
    - From Boas, 1925 Feb. 5
    - From Boas, 1926 May 18
    - From Boas, 1927 Sep. 23
    - From Boas, 1927 Nov. 9
    - From Boas, 1928 Apr. 23
    - From Boas, 1929 May 1
    - From Boas, 1929 May 15
    - From Boas, 1932 Apr. 8
    - From Boas, 1932 May 5
    - From Boas, 1932 Oct. 13
    - From Boas, 1937 Jan. 7
    - From Boas, 1937 Mar. 11
    - From Boas, 1942 Feb. 16
    - To Boas, 1908 May 28; 4p
    - To Boas, 1911 Nov. 1
    - To Boas, 1911 Nov. 2
    - To Boas, 1912 Jan. 3
    - To Boas, 1912 Jan. 15
    - To Boas, 1912 Feb. 1
    - To Boas, 1912 Mar. 22
    - To Boas, 1912 Apr. 18
    - To Boas, 1912 May 21
    - To Boas, 1912 June 23
    - To Boas, 1912 Oct. 18
    - To Boas, 1912 Nov. 10; 4p
    - To Boas, 1912 Nov. 16; 2p
    - To Boas, 1912 Nov. 25; 3p
    - To Boas, 1912 Nov. 29; 2p
    - To Boas, 1912 Dec. 7
    - To Boas, 1912 Dec. 20
    - To Boas, 1912 Dec. 24
    - To Boas, 1912 Dec. 29
    - To Boas, 1913 Jan. 28
    - To Boas, 1913 July 11; 2p
    - To Boas, 1913 Sep. 22; 2p
    - To Boas, 1913 Nov. 3
    - To Boas, 1913 Nov. 7
    - To Boas, 1913 Nov. 21
    - To Boas, 1913 Dec. 5
    - To Boas, 1914 Feb. 22
    - To Boas, 1914 Mar. 22; 2p
    - To Boas, 1914 Mar. 30; 3p
    - To Boas, 1914 July 15
    - To Boas, 1914 Aug. 10
    - To Boas, 1914 Aug. 31
    - To Boas, 1915 Jan. 7; 4p
    - To Boas, 1915 Feb. 5
    - To Boas, 1916 Jan. 6
    - To Boas, 1916 Jan. 9
    - To Boas, 1916 Jan. 13
    - To Boas, 1916 Jan. 18
    - To Boas, 1916 Jan. 18; 3p
    - To Boas, 1916 Feb. 9
    - To Boas, 1916 Feb. 26
    - To Boas, 1916 Apr. 17
    - To Boas, 1916 Apr. 28
    - To Boas, 1916 June 19
    - To Boas, 1917 Jan. 1
    - To Boas, 1917 Jan. 30
    - To Boas, 1917 Feb. 21
    - To Boas, 1917 Apr. 21
    - To Boas, 1920 Apr. 27
    - To Boas, 1920 Apr. 28
    - To Boas, 1920 Oct. 20
    - To Boas, 1920 Dec. 7
    - To Boas, 1921 June 11
    - To Boas, 1924 Nov.?
    - To Boas, 1924 Dec. 14
    - To Boas, 1925 Jan. 8
    - To Boas, 1926 Aug. 12; 2p
    - To Boas, 1926 Aug. 20
    - To Boas, 1928 Feb. 12
    - To Boas, 1928 Apr. 10
    - To Boas, 1928 June 26
    - To Boas, 1928 Dec. 31
    - To Boas, 1929 Feb. 12
    - To Boas, 1929 May 3; 2p
    - To Boas, 1932 Mar. 24; 2p
    - To Boas, 1932 Apr. 19; 4p
    - To Boas, 1932 Apr. 29; 1 p
    - To Boas, 1932 Oct. 6
    - To Boas, 1942 Feb. 18
      - see FB to Fish Teachers Agencies, 1917 Dec. 31
    - To Andrews, H.A., 1913 Oct. 25; 2p
    - To Andrews, H.A., 1913 Nov. 1
    - To Andrews, H.A., 1914 July 15
  - Radloff, W. (Box 73)
    - From Boas, 1913 Feb. 21; 2p
    - From Boas, 1913 Feb. 28
    - From Boas, 1913 Feb. 28; 2p
    - To Boas, 1903 Sep. 28; 3p
    - To Boas, 1912 July 17; 1p
    - To Boas, 1913 Feb. 14
  - Rae, P.M. (Box 73)
    - To Herskovits, M.J., 1925 Feb. 2
      - enc. originally in Herskovitx, M.J., 1925 Feb. 5
  - Rainbow Bridge-Monument Valley Expedition (Box 73)
    - Kelley, T.R., 1935 Mar. 20
  - Rainey, Froelich (Box 73)
    - To Boas, 1935 July 30; 2p
  - Ralph, J. (Box 73)
    - From Boas, 1924 Dec. 29
    - To Boas, 1924 Dec. 20
  - Ramaswamy, S.V. (Box 73)
    - From Boas, 1932 Sep. 28
    - To Boas, 1932 June 8; 3p
    - To Boas, 1932 Nov. 29; 4p
    - From Benedict, R.F.?, 1932 July 14
    - From Janardhana, R., 1932 June 4
  - Ramos, Arthur (Box 73)
    - From Boas, 1937 June 21
    - To Boas, 1937 May 27
  - Ramsey, J.R. (Box 73)
    - From Boas, 1917 Feb. 5; 2p
  - Rand School (Box 73)
    See Bohn, Wm. E.
    See Field, Geo.
  - Randall, John Herman Jr. (Box 73)
    - See Pegram, G.B. to Cabanellas, 1937 Feb. 11
    - See FB open letter, Spain, replies, 1938 Jan.
    - See Wiener, Philip Paul, 1938 Nov. 30
  - Randall-Maciver (Box 73)
    - From Boas, 1905 Mar. 27
  - Ranke (Box 73)
    - From Boas, 1905 Apr. 22
  - Ranke, Hermann (Box 73)
    - From Boas, 1920 Apr. 28
    - To Boas, 1920 Feb. 19; 4p
      - enc. "Agyptologisches Inst. der U. Heidelberg", 1920 Feb. 19
    - To Boas, 1920 May 8
    - To Boas, 1930 Sep. 25
  - Ransom, J.H. (Box 73)
    - From Boas, 1909 Dec. 15
    - To Boas, 1909 Oct. 19
  - Ransome, J. (Box 73)
    - From Boas, 1935 Sep. 23
    - From Boas, 1935 Sep. 30
    - To Boas, 1935 Sep. 27
    - To Boas, 1935 Oct. 10
  - Rao, Kodanda (Box 73)
    - From Boas, 1936 Feb. 3
    - From Boas, 1936 Feb. 21
    - To Boas, 1936 Jan. 12
      - (enc./copy of Mahtma Gandhi's letter of introduction, and Sapir, E.), 1935 Jan. 29
    - To Boas, 1936 Jan. 11
    - To Boas, 1936 Jan. 16; 2p
    - To Boas, 1936 Feb. 6
  - Raphael, Ruth (Box 73)
    - To Boas, 1927 Apr. 2
  - Rapkine, Louis (Box 73)
    - From Boas, 1940 Jan. 7
    - To Boas, 1940 Dec. 31
  - Rapkine, N.L.T. (Box 73)
    - From Simpson, 1940 Nov. 28
  - Rappaport, David (Box 73)
    - From Boas, 1909 Mar. 26
    - From Boas, 1909 Apr. 28
      - also to Schwarz & Jaegendorf, 1909 May 6
    - From Boas, 1909 June 5
    - From Boas, 1909 June 29
    - From Boas, 1909 July 2
    - To Boas, 1909 July 19
  - Rappleye, W.C. (Box 73)
    - From Boas, 1935 May 27
    - To Boas, 1935 June 5
      - enc. clipping, N.Y. Herald Trib., 1935 May 30
  - Rathbone, Josephine A. (Box 73)
    - From Boas, 1934 Apr. 12
    - To Boas, 1934 Mar. 5; 2p
  - Rathbun, R., U.S. Nat'l Mus. (Box 73)
    - From Boas, 1904 May 24
    - From Boas, 1906 Mar. 7
    - From Boas, 1907 Feb. 14
    - From Boas, 1909 July 14; 3p
    - From Boas, 1910 Aug. 19
    - To Boas, 1906 June 12
    - To Boas, 1907 Feb. 9
    - To Boas, 1907 Apr. 6
    - To Boas, 1910 Aug. 17
    - To Farrand, L., 1904 July 1
  - Rathjens, W.F. (Box 73)
    - To Boas, 1925 Nov. 22
  - Ratner, Jos. (Box 73)
    - From Boas, 1936 Oct. 30
    - To Boas, 1938 Jan. 4
    - To Boas, 1936 Oct. 23
  - Rattenmann (Box 73)
    - From Boas, 1905 Mar. 27
  - Ratzel, F. (Box 73)
    - To Boas, 1889 Nov. 6
    - To Boas, 1897 Mar. 29; 4p
    - To Boas, 1897 June 8; 4p
  - Rau, C. (Box 73)
    - From Boas, 1926 Oct. 6
    - From Boas, 1926 Oct. 21
    - From Boas, 1926 Oct. 29; 2p
    - From Boas, 1927 Aug. 12
    - To Boas, 1926 Nov. 15; 2p
    - To Boas, 1926 Dec. 31
    - To Boas, 1927 Jan. 5
    - To Boas, 1927 Oct. 29; 2p
    - To Bryan, R. (FB's sec'y), 1927 July 29
    - To FB's Berlin sister?, 1926 Dec. 20
    - To Wissler, C., 1926 Aug. 30
  - Rautenstrauch, Walter B. (Box 74)
    - From Boas, 1939 Feb. 21
    - From Boas, 1940 Nov. 11
      - (reply on margin), 1940 Dec. 5
      - same to Finkelstein, 1941 Dec. 22
      - Fairchild, 1941 Dec. 22
      - Lynd, 1941 Dec. 22
      - Mitchell, 1941 Dec. 22
      - Dearborn, 1941 Dec. 22
    - From Boas, 1942 Oct. 12
    - To Boas, 1939 Feb. 20
    - To Boas, 1939 Oct. 12
    - To Boas, 1939 Oct. 12
    - See Pegram, G.B. to Cabanellas, 1937 Feb. 11
    - See FB to Carlson, A.J., 1940 May 24
    - See FB to Rauthenstrauch, 1940 May 24
    - To Boas (margin), 1940 Dec. 5
    - To Boas, 1941 Mar. 21
      - (enc. Coffin, Henry S. to Turner, Lily), 1941 Mar. 19
    - To Boas, 1941 Nov. 7
    - See FB to NY Times, 1942 Oct. 26
    - See FB to NY Post, 1942 Oct. 26
    - To Dunn, L.C., 1938 Jan. 10
    - To Gaston-Heye, H., 1940 Dec. 31
    - To Bagley, W.C., 1942 Feb. 9
    - To Butler, N.M. enc. with FB open letter, 1938 Mar. 3
  - Ravené, Gustav (Box 74)
    - To Boas (see special folder marked Ravené), 1887 Sep. 16
    - To Boas, 1889 Mar. 4; 2p
    - To Boas, 1889 Dec. 17; 3p
    - To Boas, 1889 Dec. 20; 2p
    - To Boas, 1890 Jan. 14; 6p
    - To Boas, 1890 Feb. 19; 3p
    - To Boas, 1890 Mar. 14; 2p
    - To Boas, 1890 Mar. 19; 5p
    - To Boas, 1890 Aug. 20; 4p
    - To Boas, 1892 Sep. 29; 2p
    - To Boas, 1892 Dec. 26; 2p
    - To Boas, 1893 Feb. 24; 4p
    - To Boas, 1893 Mar. 27; 2p
    - To Boas, 1897 Apr. 15
    - To Boas, 1898 June 12
    - To Boas, 1898 Sep. 14; 2p
    - To Boas, 1898 Sep. 25; 7p
    - To Boas, 1898 Sep. 30
    - To Boas, 1899 Jan. 5; 4p
    - To Boas, 1905 Apr. 4; 4p
    - To Boas Family, 1897 Mar. 9; 2p
    - To Boas, Mrs. Sofia, 1896 Dec. 2
    - To Boas, 1897 Jan. 19
    - To Boas, 1897 Sep. 25; 2p
    - From Chwatal, H., 1889 Nov. 26
    - From George, Rudolf, 1889 Aug. 20
    - To Urbach, 1897 Jan. 12; 2p
    - To Urbach, 1897 Apr. 15; 4p
  - Ravensl, W. de C. (Box 74)
    - To Boas, 1904 May 12
  - Ravizza, Mrs. (Box 74)
    - From Ronchitti, 1897 Feb. 8
  - Rawlins, E.E. (Box 74)
    - From Boas, 1923 Nov. 3
  - Ray, Verne F. (Box 74)
    - From Boas, 1931 Dec. 7
    - To Boas, 1931 Nov. 30
    - To Sapir, E., 1937 May 30
  - Raymond, J.H. (Box 74)
    - To Hodges, N.D.C.?, 1888 Apr. 26
  - Raymond, R.M. (Box 74)
    - To Boas, 1917 Jan. 19
  - Razey, Sylvia W. (Mrs. J.L.) and J.L. (Box 74)
    - From Boas, 1939 Mar. 2
    - To Boas, 1939 Mar. 1
    - From Boas, 1939 Nov. 30
    - From Boas, 1940 May 6
    - To Boas, 1939 Nov. 28
    - To Boas, 1940 May 1
  - Razovsky, Celia. -- RE: (Refugees from Germany) (Box 74)
    - 1935 Dec. 5
    - From Boas, 1938 Sep. 19
    - From Boas, 1939 Apr. 3
    - From Boas, 1939 Apr. 6
      - See Boas, F. to Johnson, Alvin, 1940 Feb. 2
    - From Boas, 1940 Feb. 2
    - From Boas, 1942 Apr. 13
    - To Boas, 1933 Nov. 27
    - To Boas, 1935 Dec. 6
      - enc. Spivak, R.G. to CR of 1938 July 8, 1938 July 22
      - enc. Hahn, B.R. to CR, 1938 July 27
      - enc. Scharff, Mrs. A.R. to CR, 1938 Aug. 1
    - To Boas, 1938 Aug. 3
    - To Boas, 1938 Aug. 8
    - To Boas, 1938 Sep. 12
    - To Boas, 1938 Sep. 13
    - To Boas, 1939 Apr. 7
    - Form letter, 1939 Apr. 19; 2p
    - See FB to Diehl, 1938 Aug. 30
    - From Hahn, B.R., 1938 July 22
    - To Scharff, Mrs. A.R., 1938 Aug. 1
    - From Scharff, Mrs. A.R., 1938 July 24
    - From Small, Mrs. David M., 1938 July 22
    - From Spivack, R.G., 1938 July 8
      - (enc. CR, July 22)
  - RCA Victor Co., Inc. (Box 74)
    - To Boas from Briggs, H.L., 1920 June 8
  - Reabal, L.S. (Box 74)
    - To Boas, 1928 Dec. 31
  - Read, Mary L. (Box 74)
    - From Boas, 1909 Apr. 27
    - To Boas, 1909 Apr. 26
  - Read, Wm. A. (Box 74)
    - To Boas, 1913 Feb. 22
  - Reale Accademia d'Italia (Box 74)
    - To Boas from Parrlini, 1932 Apr. 21
  - Rebeca Shelley Repatriation Committee (Box 74)
    - To Boas, 1933 Mar. 11
  - Rebel, Hans (Box 74)
    - From Boas, 1927 Sep. 20
  - Reche, O. (Box 74)
    - From Boas, 1925 Mar. 12
    - From Boas, 1927 Dec. 15
    - To Boas, 1927 Nov. 28; 2p
    - To Boas, 1928 Jan. 18; 2p
  - Recht, C. (Box 74)
    - To Boas, 1921 Apr. 6
  - Recinos, AdriC!n (Box 74)
    - To Boas, 1917 July 24
    - To Boas, 1917 Oct. 9
  - Reckarts (Box 74)
    - See FB to Engerrand, G.C., 1913 Oct. 31
  - Redefer, F.L. (Box 74)
    - See Lindeman, E.O., 1936 June 26
    - From Durlach, T.M., 1936 June 28
    - To Durlach, T.M., 1936 July 14
  - Redfearn, S.F. (Mrs. D.H.) (Box 74)
    - To Boas, 1920 Sep. 24
  - Redfield, Robert (Box 74)
    - From Boas, 1941 Jan. 10
  - Redlich, Josef (Box 74)
    - From Boas, 1930 Oct. 13
    - To Boas, 1930 Sept. 30
  - Reeck, Emerich (Box 74)
    - From Boas, 1924 Dec. 16
    - From Boas, 1929 Oct. 30; 2p
    - From Boas, 1930 Feb. 7
    - To Boas, 1924 Dec. 5 and 1927 Jan. 1
    - To Boas, 1927 Apr. 4
    - To Boas, 1929 Oct. 21
    - To Boas, 1929 Nov. 11
    - To Boas, 1930 Jan. 22
  - Reed, E.E. (Box 74)
    - Abstract, 1917 Dec. 31; 1p
    - Abstract, 1917 Dec. 31
  - Reed, Mrs. (Box 74)
    - From Boas, 1939 May 15
  - Reed, T.B. (Box 74)
    - To Boas, 1915 Feb. 13
  - Reeder, C. Wells (Box 74)
    - To Boas, 1906 Oct. 3
    - To Boas, 1907 Apr. 5
    - To Boas, 1920 May 20
  - Reeds, C.A. (Box 74)
    - To Boas, 1915 June 16
    - To Boas, 1915 July 18
    - To Boas, 1915 Nov. 8
  - Reese, A.M. (Box 74)
    - From Boas, 1940 Sep. 24
    - From Boas, 1941 Dec. 4
    - To Boas - pamphlet enc., 1940 Sep. 20
  - Reese, Gustave (Box 74)
    - From Boas, 1937 Oct. 11
    - To Boas, 1937 Oct. 6
  - Refsdal, T.A. (Box 74)
    - From Boas, 1925 Dec. 4
    - From Boas, 1926 June 25; 2p
    - From Boas, 1931 Apr. 2
    - From Boas, 1931 Apr. 25
    - To Boas, 1925 Sep. 5
    - To Boas, 1926 Nov. 30
    - To Boas, 1927 Jan. 12
    - To Boas, 1931 Jan. 29
    - To Boas, 1931 May 12
  - Regnani or Regnano, E. (Box 74)
    - To Boas, 1910 Apr. 16
    - To Boas, 1910 May 22
    - To Boas, 1910 June 9
  - The Regularization of Industry (Box 74)
    - enc. with Hayden, P.M., 1934 May 15; 2p
  - Regur, Dorothy -- (Sec'y to Dr. Seashore) (Box 74)
    - To Boas, 1936 Jan. 13
  - Rehm, R. (Box 74)
    - From Boas, 1923 Mar. 5
  - Rehn, James A.G. (Box 74)
    - From Boas, 1920 Dec. 31
  - Rei-----, O.E. (Box 74)
    - To Boas, 1931 Aug. 14
  - Reich, N.J. (Box 74)
    - From Boas, 1936 Dec. 7
    - To Boas, 1936 Oct. 15
    - To Boas, 1936 Nov. 1
    - To Boas, 1936 Dec. 9
  - Reichard, Gladys A. (Box 74)
    Native American Images note
    Navajo
    - From Boas, 1919 May 20
    - From Boas, 1919 July 11
    - From Boas, 1922 Nov. 17
    - From Boas, 1922 Oct. 9; 2p
    - From Boas, 1923 Jan. 27
    - From Boas, 1923 Jan. 29
    - From Boas, 1923 Mar. 6
    - From Boas, 1923 Mar. 9
    - From Boas, 1926 June 24
    - From Boas, 1926 July 19
    - From Boas, 1926 Sep. 14; 2p
    - From Boas, 1926 Nov. 4; 3p
    - From Boas, 1927 Feb. 1
    - From Boas, 1927 Feb. 23
    - From Boas, 1927 Mar. 9
    - From Boas, 1927 Apr. 4; 2p
    - From Boas, 1927 Apr. 9
    - From Boas, 1927 Apr. 22
    - From Boas, 1927 May 7; 2p
    - From Boas, 1927 May 23
    - From Boas, 1927 June 9
    - From Boas, 1927 June 10
    - From Boas, 1929 May 27
    - From Boas, 1931 July 15
    - From Boas, 1931 June 6; 1p
    - From Boas, 1932 June 3
    - From Boas, 1933 June 26
    - From Boas, 1937 July 7
    - From Boas, 1938 Sep. 8; 3p
    - From Boas, 1938 Sep. 19
    - From Boas, 1938 Dec. 5
    - From Boas, 1938 Dec. 19
    - From Boas, 1939 June 22
    - see FB open letter, 1941 Nov. 6
    - To Boas, 1919 May 18; 3p
    - To Boas, 1919 May 20; 2p
    - To Boas, 1919 May 27; 2p
    - To Boas, 1921 Sep. 29; 2p
    - To Boas, 1921 Sep. 29; 1p
    - To Boas, 1922 Sep. 26; 6p
    - To Boas, 1922 Oct. 13; 2p
    - To Boas, 1922 Nov. 19; 5p
    - To Boas, 1922 Nov. 26; 2p
    - To Boas, 1922 Dec. 22; 2p
      - enc. "Coyote...", 1923 Jan. 11; 5p
    - To Boas, 1923 Feb. 8
    - To Boas, 1923 Mar. 1; 2p
    - To Boas, 1923 Mar.?
    - To Boas, 1923 June 19; 4p
    - To Boas, 1923 July 5; 4p
    - To Boas, 1924 Aug. 1; 6p
    - To Boas, 1925 Oct. 28; 2p
    - To Boas, 1926 June 28; 2p
    - To Boas, 1926 July 31; 2p
    - To Boas, 1926 Aug. 21; 2p
    - To Boas, 1926 Sep. 5; 2p
    - To Boas, 1926 Oct. 2; 4p
    - To Boas, 1926 Oct. 25; 2p
    - To Boas, 1926 Nov. 4; 2p
    - To Boas, 1926 Nov. 2; 2p
    - To Boas, 1926 Nov. 26; 2p
    - To Boas, 1926 Dec. 31
    - To Boas, 1926 Dec. 31
    - To Boas, 1927 Feb. 13; 4p
    - To Boas, 1927 Mar. 6; 4p
    - To Boas, 1927 Mar. 22; 5p
    - To Boas, 1927 Apr. 22
    - To Boas, 1927 Apr. 25; 4p
    - To Boas, 1927 May 5
    - To Boas, 1927 May 10; 2p
    - To Boas, 1927 June 26; 2p
    - To Boas, 1927 July 12; 5p
    - To Boas, 1927 July 19; 3p
    - To Boas, 1927 July 21
    - To Boas, 1927 July 21; 2p
    - To Boas, 1927 July 25; 2p
    - To Boas, 1927 July 26; 2p
    - To Boas, 1927 July 31; 4p
    - To Boas, 1927 Aug. 7; 4p
    - To Boas, 1927 Aug. 11; 4p
    - To Boas, 1927 Aug. 16; 2p
    - To Boas, 1927 Aug. 20; 2p
    - To Boas, 1927 Aug. 24
    - To Boas, 1927 Aug. 31; 3p
    - To Boas, 1927 Sep. 29
    - To Boas, 1927 Dec. 31
    - To Boas, 1927 Dec. 31; 2p
    - To Boas, 1929 June 12; 6p
    - To Boas, 1929 July 3; 10p
    - To Boas, 1929 July 6; 1
    - To Boas, 1929 Aug. 29; 8p
    - To Boas, 1929 July 26; 4p
    - To Boas, 1930 Dec.31; 2p
    - To Boas, 1931 May 29; 2p
    - To Boas, 1931 June 27; 2p
    - To Boas, 1931 July 10; 3p
      - enc. Knox, Lucy to GAR, 1931 July 11
    - To Boas, 1931 July 26; 2p
    - To Boas, 1932 June 6; 2p
    - To Boas, 1932 June 26
    - To Boas, 1932 July 13; 3p
    - To Boas, 1932 July 15; 2p
    - To Boas, 1932 Aug. 16; 2p
    - To Boas, 1933 June 12; 2p
    - To Boas, 1933 July 2; 2p
    - To Boas, 1933 July 11; 2p
    - To Boas, 1934 June 17; 2p
    - To Boas, 1934 Aug. 20; 2p
    - To Boas, 1934 July 4; 2p
    - To Boas, 1934 July 17; 2p
      - enc. Navajo newpapers, 1934 July 29; 2p
    - To Boas, 1935 Aug. 20; 2p
    - To Boas, 1935 July 7; 2p
    - To Boas, 1936 June 23
    - To Boas, 1936 July 2; 8p
    - To Boas, 1936 July 10; 2p
    - To Boas, 1936 July 21; 2p
    - To Boas, 1936 July 28
    - To Boas, 1936 Aug. 29; 6p
    - To Boas, 1936 Sep. 6; 3p
    - To Boas, 1936 Dec. 31; 2p
    - To Boas, 1936 Jan. 3; 2p
    - To Boas, 1937 Jan. 17; 2p
    - To Boas, 1937 June 8
    - To Boas, 1937 June 29; 2p
    - To Boas, 1937 July 9; 2p
    - To Boas, 1938 July 15
    - To Boas, 1938 July 17; 2p
    - To Boas, 1938 Sep. 4; 2p
    - To Boas, 1938 Sep. 13
    - To Boas, 1938 Oct. 11; 2p
    - To Boas, 1938 Oct. 30; 2p
    - To Boas, 1938 Nov. 16; 2p
    - To Boas, 1938 Nov. 30
    - To Boas, 1938 Dec. 14; 2p
    - To Boas, 1938 Dec. 28; 2p
    - To Boas, 1939 July 3
    - To Boas, 1939 Aug. 10; 2p
    - To Boas, 1939 Aug. 13
    - To Boas, 1939 Dec. 31
    - To Boas, 1940 Sep. 13; 2p.
    - Reichard -- to Cowan, J.M., 1943 May 3
    - From Schmidt, 1930 June 2
    - To "Frances", 1926 July 28; 2p
    - To Jacobs, Paula, 1938 Dec. 4
    - From Knox, Lucy see 7/11, 1931 May 20
    - To McDonald, D.A., 1935 Feb. 13
    - From Setzler, F.M., 1937 Feb. 4
  - Reichard, Lilian (Box 74)
    - From Boas, 1939 Sep. 11
    - To Boas, 1939 July 6
    - To Boas, 1939 Sep. 12
  - Reiche, Carlos -- (same as Karl below?) (Box 74)
    - From Boas, 1913 Oct. 31
    - From Boas, 1915 Sep. 27; 3p
    - From Boas, 1919 May 17
    - From Boas, 1919 July 25
    - To Boas, 1914 Oct. 17
    - To Boas, 1919 July 1
    - From Hunter, A., 1929 July 1
    - From Hunter, A., 1929 Nov. 6
  - Reiche, Frida (Mrs.) (Box 74)
    - From Boas, 1930 Mar. 24
    - To Boas, 1929 Oct. 27; 4p
      - enc. Hunter, A. of N.Y. Life Ins., copy plus, 1929 July 1
      - hers to him, copy, 1929 Oct. 16
    - To Boas, 1929 Nov.?; 4p
    - To Boas, 1930 Feb. 28; 2p
    - To Boas, 1931 Feb. 19; 2p
    - To N.Y. Life, copy, 1929 Oct. 16
      (see above)
  - Reiche, Karl -- (same as Carlos above?) (Box 74)
    - From Boas, 1913 Oct. 31
    - also see FB To Engerrand, 1913 Oct. 31
    - From Boas, 1914 Sep. 24
    - From Boas, 1915 Dec. 11
    - To Boas, 1911 Dec. 25
    - To Boas, 1912 Feb. 14; 2p
    - To Boas, 1912 Mar. 13
    - To Boas, 1912 Aug. 17; 2p
    - To Boas, 1912 Sep. 16
    - To Boas, 1913 Mar. 9; 2p
    - To Boas, 1914 Aug. 14
    - To Boas, 1914 Sep. 22
    - To Boas, 1914 Oct. 22
    - To Boas, 1914 Nov. 5
    - To Boas, 1915 Feb. 3
    - To Boas, 1915 Mar. 5
    - To Boas, 1915 Mar. 29
    - To Boas, 1915 May 25; 2p
    - To Boas, 1915 Sep. 12
    - To Boas, 1915 Oct. 23
    - To Boas, 1915 Nov. 1
    - To Boas, 1915 Nov. 12
    - To Boas, 1915 Dec. 1
    - To Boas, 1915 Dec. 1
    - To Boas, 1916 Jan. 24
    - To Boas, 1917 Jan. 14
    - To Boas, 1917 Mar. 11
    - To Boas, 1923 Dec. 18; 2p
    - To Boas, 1924 June 23; 2p
    - To Boas, Helene, 1915 Feb. 15
  - Reichel, G.A., German Consul General (Box 74)
    - From Boas, 1928 May 16; 2p
    - To Boas, 1928 May 7
  - Reichenbach, Mrs. L. (Box 74)
    - From Boas, 1936 Jan. 6
    - From Boas, 1936 Jan. 13
    - To Boas, 1936 Jan. 9; 3p
  - Reichert, Ernst (Box 74)
    - From Boas, 1936 May 18
    - To Boas, 1935 July 4 and 14
    - Enc. from Cummins, H., 1935 Sep. 6
    - and to Cummins, H., 1935 Sep. 9
    - with, 1935 Sep. 9
    - To Boas, 1935 Dec. 17; 2p
    - To Boas, 1936 Apr. 16
    - To Boas, 1936 Dec. 5; 2p
  - Reichert, Victor E. (Box 74)
    - To Boas, 1942 May 12; 2p
  - Reichling, G.A. (Box 74)
    - To Boas, 1917 Mar. 15
  - Reichsministerium des Innern (Box 74)
    - From Kerkhof, Franz and enc., 1932 Aug. 9
  - Reichstagsabgeordneter Erkelenz (Box 74)
    (also see Erkelenz, Anton)
    - To Boas, 1928 Apr. 23
  - Reichszentrale für naturwissenschaftliche Berichterstattung (Box 74)
    See Kerkhof, Karl
  - Reid, A.E. (Box 74)
    - To Boas, 1908 June 3
  - Reid, R.W. (Anatomy, Aberdeen University) (Box 74)
    - To Boas, 1894 Feb. 8
  - Reid, W.A. (Box 74)
    - To Butler, N.M., 1905 June 20
  - Reimann, E. (Box 74)
    - To Boas, 1933 Aug. 23; 2p
    - To or from Ernst Vohsen, Aktionsgesellschaft, 1930 Aug. 26
    - To or from Ernst Vohsen, Aktionsgesellschaft, 1930 Sep. 1
  - Reimer, Otto E. (Box 74)
    - From Boas, 1927 Dec. 16
    - From Boas, 1927 Dec. 19
    - From Boas, 1927 Dec. 21
    - From Boas, 1927 Dec. 31
    - From Boas, 1928 Jan. 16
    - From Boas, 1928 Jan. 18
    - From Boas, 1928 Jan. 18
    - From Boas, 1928 Jan. 24
    - From Boas, 1928 Jan. 30
    - From Boas, 1928 Jan. 31
    - To Boas, 1931 Aug 14
    - To Boas, 1927 Dec. 17
    - From Gramm, Hans, 1928 Jan. 13